Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 70, folder: 4 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Small Business Administration: What it is, What is Does, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Small Business Administration: What it is, What is Does, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: A Resolution Creating a Select Committee to Conduct Studies and Investigations of the Problems of Small Business, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
    December 23, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: A Resolution Creating a Select Committee to Conduct Studies and Investigations of the Problems of Small Business, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
    December 29, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: A Resolution Creating a Select Committee to Conduct a Study and Investigation of the Problems of Small Business, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
    February 8, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: A Resolution Creating a Select Committee to Conduct a Study and Investigation of the Problems of Small Business, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
    December 18, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: A Resolution Creating a Select Committee to Conduct a Study and Investigation of the Problems of Small Business, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Box: 70, folder: 5 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: A List of Management Research Summaries, Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Box: 70, folder: 6 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Management Aids for Small Business No. 18, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
    December 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Management Aids for Small Business No. 19, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
    January 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Management Aids for Small Business No. 1, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
    June 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Management Aids for Small Business No. 8, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
    August 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Management Aids for Small Business No. 6, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
    July 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Management Aids for Small Business No. 7, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Management Aids for Small Business No. 5, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Management Aids for Small Business No. 28, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
    May 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Management Aids for Small Business No. 27, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
    April 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Management Aids for Small Business No. 26, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Management Aids for Small Business No. 25, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
    March 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Management Aids for Small Business No. 24, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: Management Aids for Small Business No. 23, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Management Aids for Small Business No. 21, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
    February 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Management Aids for Small Business No. 22, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Item 16: Management Aids for Small Business No. 20, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Item 17: Management Aids for Small Business No. 19, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Item 18: Management Aids for Small Business No. 18, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Item 19: Management Aids for Small Business No. 17, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Item 20: Management Aids for Small Business No. 2, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Item 21: Management Aids for Small Business No. 3, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Item 22: Management Aids for Small Business No. 4, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Item 23: Management Aids for Small Business No. 16, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
    November 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Management Aids for Small Business No. 15, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Item 25: Management Aids for Small Business No. 14, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
    October 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Management Aids for Small Business No. 13, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Item 27: Management Aids for Small Business No. 12, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
    September 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Management Aids for Small Business No. 11, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Item 29: Management Aids for Small Business No. 10, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Item 30: Management Aids for Small Business No. 9, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Box: 70, folder: 7 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Objectives of the Social Security Administration, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: 1957 in Review, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
- Box: 70, folder: 8 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Social Security Data: Their Potential Research Uses, Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    By Ida C. Merriam. Item is in English.
- Box: 70, folder: 9 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Objectives of the Social Security Administration, Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Professional Opportunities in Social Security, Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
- Box: 70, folder: 10 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Employee Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Employee Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 70, Folder 10)
- Box: 70, folder: 11 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Joe the Genie of Steel, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: The Return of Joe the Genie of Steel, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Correspondance with Mr. Stevens, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
    June 5, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Letter to Members of Management, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
    August 13, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Letter to All Employees, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
    June 21, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Letter to All Employees, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Labor Relations in U.S. Steel, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
    September 26, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Communication in United States Steel: What, When, Where, Why, How, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: Giant Steel Works Rises on Pennsylvania Pasture, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
    May 1, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Editorial A Crime, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
    July 16, 1909. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Recognition and Bargaining Unit, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Item 12: Technical Paper: Business Administration and Economics Volume VII, Number 98, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
    By R. Heath Larry. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Fax Sheets, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Item 14: Fax Sheets, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Item 15: To the Employees of United States Steel Company, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
    May 9, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: News Release from Hill and Knowlton, Inc., Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
    June 18, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Editorial Judgement on the Steel Wage Case, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
    August 15, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: United States Steel's Reply to Demands of the United Steelworkers of America (CIO), Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
    July 6, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Letter to All Employees, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Item 20: Technical Paper: Business Administration and Economics Volume VI, Number 62--Grievance Handling, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
    By Peter C. Pianta. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Editorial Judgement on the Steel Wage Case, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
    August 8-14. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Letter to All Employees, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
    June 13, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Item 24: A Strike Against Self-Help, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
    October 1, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Technical Paper: Business Administration and Economics, Volume XI Number 19, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Item 26: Aftermath in Steel, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
    By Roger M. Blough. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Development of Union Responsibility Through Management Effort, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
    By John A. Stevens. November 15, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Labor Relations in U.S. Steel, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
    By John A. Stephens. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: The Steel Negotiations and You, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Item 30: Sub: Explanation of Steel Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan with Appended Complete Text, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Item 31: Technical Paper: Business Administration and Economics, Volume X Number 29- Steel's Human Relations Committee, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Item 32: Technical Paper: Business Administration and Economics, Volume X Number 29- Steel's Human Relations Committee, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Item 33: Technical Paper: Business Administration and Economics, Volume VIII Number 53- Steel Collective Bargaining in the '60's, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
    By R. Conrad Cooper. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Letter to Employees of United States Steel, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
    August 21, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Letter to the Employees of United States Steel, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
    July 15, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Industrial Relations for the Future, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Item 37: The Steel Negotiations and You, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Item 38: Agreement Between United States Steel Corporation and the Salaried Employees Association, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
    July 1, 1954. Item is in English.
- Box: 70, folder: 12 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    May 1972. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    May 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    May 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    November 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    August 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 9: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 10: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    November 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 12: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 13: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    August 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    May 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 16: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 17: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 18: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 19: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    November 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 21: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    August 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 23: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 24: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 25: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    February 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 27: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 28: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    November 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 30: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 31: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    August 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 33: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 34: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    May 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 36: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 37: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 38: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    February 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 40: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    November 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 42: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    August 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 43: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 44: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 45: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    February 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 46: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 47: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    August 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 48: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 49: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 50: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    November 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 51: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 52: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    August 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 53: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    May 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 54: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    February 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 55: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    November 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 56: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    May 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 57: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    February 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 58: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    May 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 59: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    November 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 60: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 61: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 62: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 63: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    August 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 64: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    May 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 65: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    August 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 66: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    November 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 67: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    February 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 68: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    May 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 69: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    August 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 70: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    November 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 71: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    May 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 72: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    August 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 73: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    Novembver 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 74: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    February 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 75: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    May 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 76: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    August 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 77: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    November 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 78: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    February 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 79: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 80: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    August 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 81: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    November 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 82: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    February 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 83: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    May 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 84: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    August 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 85: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    November 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 86: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    February 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 87: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    May 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 88: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 89: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    November 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 90: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    February 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 91: United States Steel Corporation Annual Report 1973, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 92: United States Steel Corporation Annual Report 1973, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 93: United States Steel Corporation Annual Report 1972, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 94: United States Steel Corporation Annual Report 1971, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 95: United States Steel Corporation Annual Report 1960, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 96: United States Steel Corporation Annual Report 1972, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 97: United States Steel Corporation Annual Report 1970, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 98: United States Steel Corporation Annual Report 1967, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
- Box: 70, folder: 13 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    August 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    November 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    November 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    November 1972. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 11: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    August 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    November 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 14: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    August 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Monthly Digest of Technical Papers, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    March-May 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Health Society, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    By R. Conrad Cooper. July 29, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    May 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 19: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    May 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 21: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 22: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 23: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 24: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 25: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 26: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 27: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 28: Employee Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 29: Annual Digest of Technical Papers, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 30: Reading List of Publications and Catalog of Visual Aids offered by United States Steel for Elementary and Secondary Schools, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 31: Memorandum: Special Committee on Aging, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 32: Annual Digest of Technical Papers, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 33: Order Form, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 34: Annual Digest of Technical Papers, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 35: Your Visit to Gary Sheet and Tin Mill, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 36: Curtain Time: The story of how arcitect Wilbur Jones satisfied a budget-minded client, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 37: The Bridge That's Already too Long, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 38: EQ '74: A Report on Environmental Quality, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 39: United States Steel Corporation Annual Report 1970, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 40: United States Steel Corporation Annual Report 1969, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 41: Steel Facts, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    Winter 1972. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: United States Steel Corporation Quarterly Earning Report, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    June 30, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Communicationg with EmployeesHow? And What?, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 44: Technical Paper: Business Administration and Economics, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    By Edgar B. Speer. Item is in English.
  - Item 45: News for Immediate Release, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    June 29. Item is in English.
  - Item 46: The Ore Miner: Tennessee Coal Iron and Railroad Company, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    Summer Issues. Item is in English.
  - Item 47: U.S. Steel News, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    April 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 48: Consolidated Statement of Income, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    July 28, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 49: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    May 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 50: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 51: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    May 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 52: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 53: The U.S. Steel Quarterly, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    November 1976. Item is in English.